Dad.
أبي.
My will
وصيتي
has been given to Lawyer Lin.
قد سُلمت إلى المحامي لين.
Your uncle
عمكم
Dad.
أبي.
Come back.
عُد.
Master.
سيدي.
Dad.
أبي.
Miss Qingtian,
الآنسة تشينغ تيان.
the police station is closed tomorrow.
غدا مركز الشرطة مغلق.
Are you free?
هل لديك وقت فراغ؟
What is it?
ماذا؟
Are you treating me to a meal?
هل تريد أن تدعوني لتناول الطعام؟
I have a friend who owns a villa in Lianxin District.
لدي صديق يملك فيلا في منطقة ليان شين.
He's invited me over tomorrow. How about it?
وقد دعاني للذهاب غدا، ما رأيك؟
There might be a feast.
ربما سيكون هناك وليمة كبيرة.
Do you want to go?
هل تريد الذهاب؟
Lianxin District?
منطقة ليان شين؟
That's the famous wealthy area in Decheng.
هذه هي المنطقة الغنية الشهيرة في مدينة دي.
Yes, it is.
نعم.
He's my elementary school classmate.
إنه زميلي في المدرسة الابتدائية.
But his father,
ولكن والده...
you should know him. His name is Lu Tianyang.
يجب أن تعرفه، اسمه لو تيان يانغ.
The chairman of Hongchang Chamber of Commerce?
رئيس غرفة التجارة هونغتشانغ.
Not bad, Gong Sunhe.
رائع يا قونغ سون هي.
I didn't expect you to have a friend from such a wealthy family.
لم أكن أعرف أن لديك صديقا من عائلة ثرية.
What are you talking about?
ما هذا الكلام؟
Don't we have someone from a wealthy family right here with us?
أليس لدينا بالفعل شخص من عائلة ثرية بيننا؟
Who is it?
من هذا؟
It's Fu Mosi.
إنها فو موسي.
Look,
انظر،
every time she goes out,
في كل مرة تخرج فيها،
she's surrounded by a group of followers.
يتبعها مجموعة من الأتباع.
It's so cool.
كم هي مثيرة للإعجاب!
There's nothing we can do about it.
لا يمكن تجنب ذلك.
She inherited Zhentong Trading Company, after all.
من يلومها وقد ورثت شركة تشن تونغ التجارية.
How many eyes are watching her now?
كم عدد العيون التي تراقبها الآن؟
Alright, that's not important anymore.
حسنًا، هذا ليس مهمًا الآن.
Will you come with me tomorrow?
هل يمكنك مرافقتي غدًا؟
Please?
من فضلك.
Okay, okay, I'll go with you.
حسنًا، حسنًا، سأرافقك.
But consider this as repaying your favor.
لكن اعتبر هذا ردًا للجميل.
Alright.
حسنًا.
See you tomorrow then.
إذن سنلتقي غدًا.
Compared to Xiao Fu's estate,
مقارنة بمزرعة فو الصغيرة،
it's smaller.
إنه أصغر.
This is Lianxin District,
هذه هي منطقة ليان شين!
where every inch of land is worth its weight in gold.
الأرض هنا تساوي وزنها ذهبًا.
How can it be compared to a suburban estate?
كيف يمكن مقارنتها بمزرعة في الضواحي؟
Ah He,
آه هي.
A Tai.
أتاي.
Long time no see.
لم نلتق منذ فترة طويلة.
It's been so long.
حقا لم نر بعضنا منذ وقت طويل.
Indeed.
نعم.
Oh my!
يا إلهي.
You...
أنت.
you...
أنت...
You've changed a lot.
لقد تغيرت كثيرا.
Have I?
حقا؟
It seems we haven't seen each other for only three or four years.
يبدو أننا لم نر بعضنا منذ ثلاث أو أربع سنوات فقط.
How much could I have changed?
ما الذي يمكن أن يتغير؟
Not at all. I remember you used to be quite skinny.
لا أعتقد ذلك، أتذكر أنك كنت نحيفا جدا في الماضي.
Like a bamboo pole.
مثل عود البامبو.
You're not wrong about that.
كلامك صحيح.
But you've lost quite a bit of weight yourself.
لكنك أنت فقدت الكثير من الوزن.
Your round belly from before is gone.
بطنك المستديرة التي كانت لديك في الماضي قد اختفت.
You used to be quite chubby, huh?
كنت بدينًا في الماضي، أليس كذلك؟
He was short and fat in middle school.
كان قصيرًا وبدينًا عندما كان في المدرسة المتوسطة.
He had a nickname, 'Globe.'
كان لديه لقب يسمى 'الكرة الأرضية'.
now you can imagine what he looked like back then.
يمكنك أن تتخيل كيف كان شكله في ذلك الوقت.
Globe?
الكرة الأرضية.
Oh, right. This is...
بالمناسبة، هذا الشخص...
Ah He.
آه هي.
Are you married?
هل تزوجت؟
I wish I was.
أتمنى ذلك.
No, no. I'm his colleague.
لا، لا. أنا زميله في العمل.
The police station happens to be closed today.
اليوم هو يوم عطلة في مركز الشرطة بالصدفة.
so I thought I'd come along with him for a visit.
فكرت في المجيء معه للتسلية قليلاً.
I'm sorry for intruding.
أعتذر عن الإزعاج.
I see.
أفهم.
However, we might need to trouble you a bit today.
ولكن قد نحتاج إلى مساعدتكم اليوم.
Trouble?
إزعاج؟
Let's talk inside.
دعونا نتحدث عن هذا في الداخل.
Atai.
يا آتاي.
Uncle.
عمي.
We have a guest at home.
لدينا ضيوف في المنزل.
Uncle, do you remember him?
عمي، هل تتذكره؟
the one who used to
إنه الذي كان
visit our home often when you were in elementary school, Gong Sun He.
يأتي للعب في منزلنا كثيرًا أيام المدرسة الابتدائية، غونغ سون هه.
Uncle, long time no see.
عمي، لم أرك منذ زمن طويل.
Gong Sun He.
غونغ سون هه.
I'm sorry,
آسف.
I've been abroad for years and rarely come back.
أنا نادرًا ما أعود لأنني أعيش في الخارج معظم الوقت.
I don't remember anymore.
لقد نسيت منذ فترة طويلة.
Since he's a childhood playmate,
بما أنه رفيق طفولتك،
please entertain him well.
فلتستقبله استقبالًا جيدًا.
You two chat, I'll take a walk in the garden.
تحدثوا أنتم وسأتمشى في الحديقة.
Anderson.
أندرسون.
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
He's my uncle's bodyguard.
إنه حارس عمي الشخصي.
By the way, Ahe,
بالمناسبة، يا هه.
what do you think of my uncle?
ما رأيك في عمي هذا؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تعني؟
I mean his appearance,
أعني مظهره،
his voice, things like that.
وصوته عندما يتحدث، وما إلى ذلك.
Does he seem familiar?
هل يبدو مألوفًا؟
Well,
حسنًا...
it's been so many years, how could I remember?
كيف لي أن أتذكر بعد كل هذه السنوات؟
What's wrong?
ماذا؟
Don't you recognize your own uncle?
ألا تتعرف على عمك؟
When I was in elementary school,
عندما كنت في المدرسة الابتدائية،
he moved abroad.
انتقل للعيش في الخارج.
He only came back three years ago.
عاد فقط قبل ثلاث سنوات.
But I always feel
لكنني أشعر دائمًا
there's something different about him.
أن هناك شيئًا مختلفًا.
Are you suspecting he's not your uncle?
هل تشك في أنه ليس عمك؟
But isn't your father at home?
ألكن أليس والدك في المنزل؟
Surely he wouldn't
من المستحيل
fail to recognize his own brother, right?
ألا يتعرف على أخيه، أليس كذلك؟
My father passed away last month due to illness.
توفي والدي الشهر الماضي بسبب المرض.
I'm sorry.
آسف.
Please accept my condolences.
أرجو أن تتقبل تعازي.
I was mentally prepared for this.
كنت مستعدًا لهذا في قلبي.
My mother passed away more than ten years ago.
توفيت والدتي أيضًا منذ أكثر من عشر سنوات.
The relatives who have met my uncle
الأقارب الذين رأوا عمي
have either passed away or moved far away.
إما توفوا أو انتقلوا إلى أماكن بعيدة جدًا.
Now, among those who have met my uncle before,
الآن، من بين الذين رأوا عمي من قبل،
besides my brother and me,
باستثنائي أنا وأخي،
I'm afraid you're the only one left.
أخشى أنك الوحيد المتبقي.
So you suspect someone is impersonating your uncle?
إذن أنت تشك في أن شخصًا ما ينتحل شخصية عمك؟
But who would do such a thing?
لكن من سيفعل شيئًا كهذا؟
If it's for inheriting the estate,
إذا كان الأمر يتعلق بتقسيم الميراث،
someone would definitely do it.
فبالتأكيد سيكون هناك من يفعل ذلك.
This is my wife, Tian Shan.
هذه زوجتي تيان شان.
To be honest, we all suspect this uncle.
صراحة، نحن جميعًا نشك في هذا العم.
We think this uncle
نعتقد أن هذا العم
might be here to claim a share of my father-in-law's inheritance.
ربما جاء من أجل الحصول على حصة من ميراث والد زوجي.
That's why he came here.
لهذا السبب جاء إلى هنا.
I don't need to introduce who my father-in-law is, right?
لا داعي للتعريف بمن كان والد زوجي، أليس كذلك؟
A month ago,
قبل شهر،
on his deathbed, he said he left a will.
قال وهو على فراش الموت إنه ترك وصية.
But we have to wait for a month
لكن يجب الانتظار لمدة شهر
until the uncle returns for the lawyer to disclose it.
حتى يعود العم قبل أن يتمكن المحامي من الإعلان عنها.
He also said that anyone not present when the will is read
وقال أيضًا إن أي شخص غير موجود عند إعلان الوصية
won't get a penny.
لن يحصل على أي شيء، ولا حتى قرش واحد.
If that's the case,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
today is the day the will is to be read?
فاليوم هو يوم إعلان الوصية.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
The lawyer won't arrive until tomorrow evening.
المحامي لن يصل حتى مساء الغد.
In other words,
هذا يعني
if we can't expose the old man's disguise when the lawyer reads the will tomorrow,
إذا لم نتمكن من كشف تنكر هذا العجوز
our share
عندما يقرأ المحامي الوصية غدًا
will be significantly reduced.
فإن الجزء الذي سنحصل عليه
I think
في رأيي
not only will our inheritance shares be reduced,
ليس فقط ستقل حصتنا من الميراث
some of us might not get anything at all.
بل إن بعض الناس لن يحصلوا على أي شيء على الإطلاق.
Who are these people anyway?
من هؤلاء الأشخاص بالضبط؟
That's my younger brother, Jing Jiang,
ذلك أخي الأصغر جينغ جيانغ
and next to him is my stepmother.
والشخص بجانبه هي زوجة أبي الثانية
She's the second wife my father married after my mother died,
أي الزوجة الثانية التي تزوجها أبي بعد وفاة أمي
her name is Xu Yazhi.
اسمها شو ياتشي.
I see.
أفهم.
In any case, before tomorrow,
على أي حال، قبل الغد
we must prove that this uncle is an impostor.
يجب أن نثبت أن هذا العم مزيف.
What's going on, brother?
ما الأمر يا أخي؟
I remember when uncle left home,
أتذكر أنه عندما غادر العم المنزل في ذلك الوقت
he did leave some photos, didn't he?
كان قد ترك بعض الصور، أليس كذلك؟
We might have lost many of them when we moved later.
ربما فقدنا الكثير منها عندما انتقلنا لاحقًا.
Hey, look, here's a photo album.
انظروا، هناك ألبوم صور هنا.
Look at this,
انظروا إلى هذا
isn't this uncle?
أليس هذا هو العم؟
I'm there next to him too.
وأنا بجانبه أيضًا.
That's right,
هذا صحيح
the one in the middle is uncle.
الشخص في الوسط هو العم.
But he's wearing a hat,
لكنه يرتدي قبعة
we can't see his face clearly.
لا يمكننا رؤية وجهه بوضوح.
Seriously,
حقًا
even if we found a photo,
حتى لو وجدنا الصورة
we still can't confirm if that old man
ما زلنا لا نستطيع التأكد من أن ذلك العجوز
is really our uncle or not.
هو العم بالفعل.
However, this photo looks
ومع ذلك، تبدو هذه الصورة
quite nostalgic indeed.
مثيرة للذكريات حقًا.
I remember
أتذكر
this photo should have been taken after uncle and father finished playing soccer
أن هذه الصورة التقطت بعد أن انتهى العم وأبي
after uncle and father finished playing soccer.
من لعب كرة القدم.
Ah, I remember now.
آه، تذكرت
Wasn't it that time when uncle
أتذكر في ذلك الوقت، ألم يكن العم
stepped on a nail
قد داس على مسمار بقدمه
and had to leave the game?
واضطر للخروج من الملعب؟
If that's the case, the real uncle
إذا كان الأمر كذلك، فإن العم الحقيقي
should have a scar on his foot.
يجب أن يكون لديه ندبة على قدمه.
If we can confirm this,
إذا تمكنا من التأكد من ذلك
we'll know if it's really him.
سنعرف ما إذا كان هو الشخص نفسه.
That's right,
هذا صحيح
we just need to check if he has a scar on his foot.
كل ما علينا فعله هو التأكد مما إذا كان لديه إصابة في قدمه أم لا.
Jingtai.
جينغتاي.
Make sure you see it clearly.
تأكد من أنك ترى بوضوح.
I understand.
فهمت.
Uncle,
عمي.
you've been abroad for so many years.
لقد أمضيت سنوات عديدة في الخارج.
you're probably not used to drinking tea.
بالتأكيد لست معتادًا على شرب الشاي.
I've poured you a cup of coffee.
لقد صببت لك فنجانًا من القهوة.
Thank you. Just put it here.
شكرًا، ضعها هنا.
Oh, Uncle, quickly take off your shoes and socks,
يا إلهي، عمي، اخلع حذاءك وجواربك بسرعة.
otherwise you'll get burned.
وإلا ستصاب بحروق.
It's fine, it's fine.
لا بأس، لا بأس.
It's okay, it's nothing.
لا مشكلة، كل شيء على ما يرام.
What?
ماذا؟
Indeed, there isn't any.
كما توقعت، لا يوجد.
Let's go.
هيا.
let's go take a look.
لنذهب ونرى.
As expected, there's nothing.
ماذا؟ لم يكن هناك شيء بالفعل.
You're referring to the scar on my left foot, right?
هل تقصد الندبة على قدمي اليسرى؟
It's here.
إنها هنا.
This happened over twenty years ago.
كان هذا منذ أكثر من عشرين عاما.
I was playing football with your father.
كنت ألعب كرة القدم مع والدك.
I accidentally stepped on a nail.
وطأت على مسمار عن غير قصد.
at that time,
في ذلك الوقت،
I lost a lot of blood.
نزف الكثير من الدم.
It later got infected.
ثم أصيبت بالالتهاب.
I almost lost this foot.
كدت أفقد هذه القدم.
So this uncle is the real deal.
إذن، هذا العم حقيقي.
Really.
حقا.
So you've been suspecting me all along.
كما توقعت، كنتم تشكون بي.
You never believed me.
لم تثقوا بي أبدا.
I knew each of you had ulterior motives.
كنت أعرف أن كل واحد منكم يخفي نوايا سيئة.
That's why
لذلك،
I hired Anderson in advance.
قمت بتوظيف أندرسون مسبقا.
to come here with me.
ليأتي معي إلى هنا.
Uncle,
عمي،
We just wanted to confirm
نحن فقط أردنا التأكد
your identity, that's all.
من هويتك فقط.
After all, we haven't seen you for so many years.
بعد كل هذه السنوات من عدم اللقاء.
And you even hired a bodyguard,
لقد وظفت حارسا شخصيا أيضا،
as if we were going to harm you.
كما لو أننا نريد إيذاءك.
Is there really no one who wants to harm me?
أحقا لا أحد يريد إيذائي؟
Take a look at this.
انظر إلى هذا.
A threatening letter.
رسالة تهديد.
I received this threatening letter before I left the country.
لقد تلقيت هذه الرسالة التهديدية قبل مغادرتي البلاد.
now you know
الآن أنتم تعرفون.
why I asked Anderson to come.
لماذا طلبت من أندرسون أن يأتي.
after so many years abroad,
بعد كل هذه السنوات في الخارج.
I have my own savings.
لدي مدخراتي الخاصة أيضًا.
I'm not interested in my brother's inheritance.
أنا لست مهتمًا بميراث أخي.
But when I saw this threatening letter,
لكن عندما رأيت هذه الرسالة التهديدية.
I had to come here to see
اضطررت للمجيء هنا لأرى بنفسي.
which ungrateful child
من هو هذا الابن العاق.
sent a threatening letter to me, their uncle.
الذي أرسل رسالة تهديد لعمه.
You ungrateful children!
أيها الأبناء العاقون.
Get out.
اخرجوا.
All of you, get out!
اخرجوا جميعًا.